http://www.stubbsrich.com/privacy-policy

Contact/
Privacy PolicyEffective date: 23 May 2018Thank you for visiting the SRA Architects website. This page provides more information on our privacy policy, what data we hold, how we use it and how we may contact you.We are committed to protecting the privacy of your data and personal information. This policy may be updated as we release new features.DefinitionsSRA Architects LLP is a limited liability partnership registered in England (Registration No: OC394598). Members: John Rich RIBA, David Beckett RIBA, Michael Rolfe RIBA. Use of the term Partner is not intended to suggest a partnership.The use of 'we' or 'us' refers to SRA Architects LLP.Address: Queen Square House, Charlotte Street, Bath, BA1 2LLPhone: +44 (0)1225 827444Email: group@sra-architects.co.ukWebsite: www.sra-architects.co.ukWhat information do we collect?We will collect certain types of data from you depending on your interaction with our website. This may include your name, your email address and your IP address. We will collect this data when:You visit our website.Contact us about our services.Sign up for our external newsletter.How do we collect this information?The type of data we collect depends on the nature of SRA Architects relationship with you. We will collect:Usage data via IP address. This does not provide us with any personal information about you, but allows us to discover more about how you use our website.Your first and last name when you contact us about our services or sign up to our periodic email newsletter.Your email address when you contact us about our services or sign up to our periodic email newsletter.How do we use the information we collect?We will only use your information to support the services we provide you and maintain the current relationship we have with you. We use the information we hold about you in the following ways:To send you periodic external newsletters to keep you in touch with what is happening within the practice, and how this may be of interest.To maintain and improve our online experience. We want to make our web experience as easy as possible for you. To do this, we collect non-personal data (IP address and what pages you've visited) to learn how we can improve.Keeping email addresses on file if you have contacted us about our architectural services.Who we share your information with and whyIn certain circumstances, we will share information:Internally within SRA Architects for purposes relating to the architectural services we provide.With Mailchimp's secure database for the sending of practice updates, Christmas cards and occasional external newsletters.With your consent, third parties directly related to the advancement and progression of architectural services with which you have commissioned us.We will never:Share your information or any information relating to you with external parties.Sell your data for marketing purposes outside of the practice.Use your data for targeting or display advertising.Use your data to send unwanted/spam/offensive content or material.What do I do if I want to know more?If you wish to access a copy of the personal data we hold about you, or you wish for this data to be updated, you can contact us at group@sra-architects.co.ukWe are committed to your data protection rights. If you want to learn more, email us at group@sra-architects.co.uk
Home/
Our Work/Our ProjectsOur Services
Studio/Our TeamJoin Us
About/Our ApproachOur Brochure
Blog/
Contact/
SRA Architects
With over 20 years’ experience designing award winning architectural projects throughout the UK, we enable people to realise their vision by applying our creative approach. Listen | Challenge | Refine | Enjoy
Terms |  Copyright 2018: SRA Architects - All rights reserved | Our Privacy PolicyLog In
Staff Login
Welcome, (First Name)!
Forgot?
Show
Stay Logged In
Log In
Enter Staff Area
(Message automatically replaces this text)
OK
My Profile
Log Out
